dramclaims.com 2019-07-07

# Privacy Policy

## General

This Privacy Policy applies to the “Settlement Website”, which has been established by Rust Consulting, Inc. (the “Claims Administrator”) to provide information about, and to receive and process claims for, the Settlement. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, we refer to the Claims Administrator and Class Counsel as “we” or “us”.

This Privacy Policy applies to information that you submit to the Claims Administrator through the Settlement Website, on paper Claim Forms, or otherwise. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that is publicly available, that is lawfully obtained from outside sources, that you may submit to other websites, or that you may submit in connection with other programs.

**We will only use your information pursuant to this Privacy Policy or as authorized by you.**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, so long as the change is consistent with the Settlement Agreement. We recommend that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure that you are familiar with our privacy practices. If at any time you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at the email or postal addresses in the last paragraph of this Privacy Policy.

If we use a capitalized term in this Privacy Policy, that term has the same meaning as in the Settlement Agreement, unless we define it otherwise in this Privacy Policy.

The Settlement Website may contain links to information at other websites. By clicking on one of these links, you are moving to another website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

## Information Collected

### Personally Identifiable

“Personally Identifiable Information” as used in this Privacy Policy is information that identifies you or can be used to identify or contact you, including your name, street address, email address, telephone number, social security number, taxpayer identification number, and your computers unique identifier information. We collect Personally Identifiable Information in a variety of places on the Settlement Website, such as when you:

  * Sign up to receive the Notice of Class Action Settlement and other information about the Settlement;
  * Contact us through the Settlement Website to request information from us or for other purposes relating to the Settlement;
  * Submit a Claim Form;

### Other Information

We may receive data sent by your browser or as a result of the Settlement Website’s use of “cookies.”

When you visit the Settlement Website, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer. We use cookies for various reasons, including to enable us to recognize when you are logged in to the Settlement Website and to provide access to your account while you are logged in, to store your language preferences and to facilitate your use of the Settlement Website. You may be able to control how cookies are used by consulting your Internet browser software.

In addition, your browser may send us information, such as your requests to the Settlement Website, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language and the date and time of your request.

## Use of Information

We will only use or disclose your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as authorized by you. We may use your information to administer the Settlement, including to respond to your inquiries, directions and requests regarding the Settlement, for the processing and administration of claims and payments (e.g., to send you amounts due under the Settlement), to effectuate the Settlement (including to use your content in accordance with the Settlement), and to improve our Settlement administration services. We also may use your information to communicate with you about the status of the Settlement and matters relating to the Settlement.  In circumstances deemed appropriate by counsel, we may use your information to communicate about other settlements and to assist you in filing a claim in other settlements.

We will not associate Personally Identifiable Information collected from you through the Settlement Website with any of your Personally Identifiable Information that we obtain from sources other than you or other than through the Settlement Website except for the uses specified by this Privacy Policy, unless such information is public or as authorized by you.

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy or as authorized by you, we will not share any of your Personally Identifiable Information with any other person. We may disclose information that you provide about your Claim so long as we do not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information. In addition, we may share information from you and others in aggregated, non-personally identifiable form with any other person, including members of the general public.

The information you provide in connection with opting out of the Settlement may be disclosed to the Court and parties to the Settlement.

We may also use information, or share information with third parties, when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with legal process or otherwise satisfy any applicable law or regulation; or (b) prevent fraud or imminent harm, ensure the security of information or address technical issues.

We may use independent contractors, vendors, and suppliers (“Outside Contractors”). If we use Outside Contractors to assist with the processing of your information, we may disclose your information to them or receive your information through them. Before disclosing any information to an Outside Contractor, we will, at a minimum, require that it agrees to comply with our obligations under this Privacy Policy with respect to information it receives from us or from you.

## Access to and Removal of Information

At any time, you may request access to our copy of your Personally Identifiable Information by contacting us at the email or postal addresses below.

You may request that we delete your Personally Identifiable Information stored by us in electronic form. We will honor your request but we are unable to guarantee that all such information will be deleted because some residual information may remain on back-up storage and other media. Please note that deletion of some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information may affect your ability to participate in the Settlement.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [privacy@rustconsulting.com](mailto:privacy@rustconsulting.com) or by postal mail via Privacy Policy, c/o Rust Consulting, Inc., 201 South Lyndale Ave, Faribault MN 55021.
